

Mauricio Sebastian Leoncio Arizaca Soto

I'm a professional dedicated to cybersecurity analysis with four years of experience in the detection, communication, and resolution of threats. Multitasking on the programming front, networking, and process management related to the cybersecurity and automation processes.

CONTACT INFORMATION

- **Address**: Av. El Sauce 395 – Surquillo, Lima, Perú

- Phone Number: (+51) 940 165 950

- Email: mau_arso98@hotmail.com

- Birthdate: 01/07/1998

- LinkedIn:

LinkedIn_profile

- GitHub:

https://github.com/Maucross?tab=repositories

- Personal web

https://maucross.github.io/mauricio_resume/

ABILITIES & SKILLS

- ✓ Information Security services
- ✓ Network security
- ✓ Incidence response
- ✓ Risk Management
- ✓ Problem solving
- ✓ Critical Thinking
- ✓ Effective Communication with English speaker clients
- ✓ Continuous Learning

EDUCATION

Bachellor in Computer and System Engineer – San Martín de $_{03/2015-12/2021}$ Porres University

Centro de Idiomas Británico – English Advance Level

03/2011 - 11/2014

CERTIFICACTIONS

Certified in Cybersecurity – CC Issued by ISC2 on July 03, 2023

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner - CCP

Issued by Amazon Web Services on August 30, 2023

SCRUM Fundamentals Certified

Issued by SCRUMstudy on July 11, 2019

Certified ISO 27001 Lead Auditor - I27001LA

Issued by Certiprof on April 20, 2024

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

Programming

o Excel (Visual Basic)

o Javascript

o Python

o HTML

I've created a python script for sending automated communication campaigns to the owners, develop an email template in HTML and automated information dashboards using macros in Excel using VB.

Scanning & Management

o Qualys VMDR

o DivvyCloud

o Prisma Cloud

o Redshift (aws)

o Jira

I've been using Qualys platform for assets and vulnerabilities management, analyze the information to provide to the owners. DivvyCloud for same but for cloud assets and intances status as same as Prisma Cloud. Backstage was the main platform for owners to receive their asset information that involves for different databases like Qualys & Redshift (AWS). Jira for tickets management and update status.

Hacking
o Burp Suite

o Linux (Kali – Parrot)

o OWASP

I use Burp suite application for testing web vulnerabilities such as XSS, XXE, CSRF we recived from pentesters by HackerOne platform. Linux OS Is were I perform some of test process. I'm familized with OWASP TOP 10 vulnerability web.

REFERENCES

Jose V. Ruiz - Senior Vulnerability Analyst | **Aynitech**

T: +1 (908) 627-2915 E: jruiz@aynitech.com

Josh Carsen - Manager, Vulnerability Management Operations • Security Cyber Defense Mgmt | **Expedia Group**

E: jcarsen@expediagroup.com

Mauricio Nair – Chief Tecnology Officer (CTO) | **Sanna**

T: +51 943 901 184

E: mauricio.nair@sanna.pe

Tito Guerra Solis – Support and IT Services Chief | Sanna

T: +51 943 445 355 E: tito.guerra@sanna.pe

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Vulnerability Analyst

02/2022 - Present

Aynitech – Benavides, Lima Perú

Aynitech provides cybersecurity assisance to Expedia Group Company (EG) where I give assistance on:

- Analysis and testing of web vulnerabilities, dockers, cloud instances. Once those issues were mitigated I deliver the information to the rest of the team and close the tickets.
- Review of patching assets and cloud instances, using cybersecurity tools to manage these information.
- Use of database to generate reports, where we gather to send to the owners each by weekly communications.
- Development and sending of automated reports to owners with vulnerable assets.
- Communication, negotiation, and resolution of questions with clients from different countries.

IT Support Analyst

Sanna Clínica El Golf – San Isidro, Lima Perú

09/2020 - 01/2022

- Guidance to users on the operation of technological systems.
- Installation and update of hardware, software and security patches.
- User maintenance, Active Directory privileges for medical and management users.
- Helpdesk service to users within the clinic for resolution of IT problems.